地球。
The earth.
地球上有一百多万种生物
There are more than a million species of life
生活在这个美丽的蓝色星球上。
living on this beautiful blue planet.
但是，现在地球上有超过15000种物种，
But, now there are more than 15,000 species on this planet,
有灭绝的危险。
that are in danger of extinction.
我们现在必须站起来。
We must stand up now.
再见。
Bye bye.
见到你。
See you.
♬现在我是一个高中生了
♪Now I am a high school student♪
我也想恋爱!
I also want to fall in love!
哦，我只是不自觉地说出来了!
Oh, I just said it unconsciously!
但我也想爱上一个人。
But I also wanna fall in love with someone.
嗯?
Huh?
啊!青山!
Ah! Aoyama!
战斗!
Fighting!
我支持你!
I'm rooting for you!
我看不见他。
I can't see him.
脸!
Face!
(宫本茂)脸了!
(Miyamoto) Face Hit!
-他做到了!——太棒了!
- He did it! - Awesome!
很帅!
So handsome!
(青山)哇!
(Aoyama) Wow!
太棒了!
Awesome!
啊!青山往这边看!
Ah! Aoyama looked this way!
这是可怕的。
It was awesome.
那个人叫青山。
That person is called Aoyama.
(东京Mew Mew New)
(Tokyo Mew Mew New)
发生了什么! ?从今天起，做正义的捍卫者!
What's Going on!? Be a Champion of Justice from Today on!
青山吗?
Aoyama?
你是说剑道俱乐部的青山正雅吗?
You mean that Aoyama Masaya from the Kendo club?
哦，他的名字叫Masaya。
Oh, his name is Masaya.
是的。青山真牛，不是吗?你不认识他!?
Yep. Aoyama is awesome, isn't he? You didn't know him!?
他是学校里最受欢迎的人!
He's the most popular person in the school!
真的吗?
Really?
你怎么不知道?
Why didn't you know that?
但我怎么知道呢?
But how could I know that?
草莓,你……
Well, Ichigo, you...
(当我跨越梦想之桥时)
(As I Crossed a Bridge of Dreams)
(当我走过梦之桥)晚上，当我读这个故事的时候，一只猫……
(As I Crossed a Bridge of Dreams) At night, when I read the story, a cat...
竞争率不是很低吗?
Isn't the competition rate bad?
你不觉得太难了吗?
Don't you think it's too difficult?
但是!
But!
他的成绩在年级中名列前茅。
His scores rank the top among the grade.
他的运动协调能力很强
He has superior motor coordination,
英俊的脸和良好的品格。
handsome face and good character.
难道不可能吗?
Isn't it impossible?
但是，但是我想多了解青山!
But, but I wanna know more about Aoyama!
嗯!
Eh!
我会帮你的!
I will help you!
这是一护的初恋!
This is Ichigo's first love!
你们两个……
Both of you...
作为回报。
In return.
如果进展顺利，就把材料给我。
If it goes well, give me the materials.
材料?
Materials?
是的，写小说的材料。
Yes, the materials for novel writing.
美和想当小说家，对吧?
Miwa wants to be a novelist, right?
——哦!-我的目标是成为一名顾问。
- Oh! - My target is to being a counselor.
顾问?
Counselor?
是的。我希望我未来的职业是关心别人的心。
Yes. I wish my future occupation is something about taking care of others' hearts.
啊。你们都在考虑未来……
Ah. Both of you are thinking about the future...
现在我们是高中生了。
Now we are high school students.
我想我们得想想自己想成为什么样的人。
I suppose we have to think what we wanna be.
一护，你想做什么?
Ichigo, what do you want to be?
啊?我…
Ah? I...
嗯…我不知道!
Hmm...I don't know!
草莓,冷静下来。
Ichigo, calm down.
不管怎样，现在你的目标是青山!
Anyway, now your target is Aoyama!
是的,这是正确的。你得先去约会!
Yes, that's right. You have to go on a date first!
好吧,好吧。
Well, okay.
太棒了!我现在能感觉到你的热情。
Great! I can feel your passion now.
——哦!——哦!
- Oh! - Oh!
对了，关于昨天发生的事…
By the way, about what happened yesterday...
青山,你……
Aoyama, you...
哦。谢谢你！
Oh. Thank you.
——先生!先生!——什么?
- Mister! Mister! - What?
我得走了。
I gotta go now.
(佐佐木)
(Sasaki)
非常感谢。
Thank you very much.
嗯。青山对环境问题很感兴趣。
Hmm. Aoyama is interested in environmental problems.
环境问题?
Environmental problems?
这听起来深。
It sounds deep.
嗯?
Huh?
(Moe:好!古板的:明白了。)
(Moe: OK! Miwa: Got it.)
(美和:我收集了很多信息!!)青山似乎喜欢动物。
(Miwa: I collected a lot of information!!) Aoyama seems to like animals.
(老谋子:我听说他自愿清理河流。)我听说他自愿清理这条河。
(Moe: I heard he volunteered to clean up the river.) I heard he volunteered to clean up the river.
嗯。他做志愿者工作。
Hmm. He does volunteer work.
Momomiya草莓。
Momomiya Ichigo.
是吗?
Yes?
嗯,你是谁?
Well, you are?
嗯?
Huh?
如果你用这个邀请他，你就可以和他约会了。
If you invite him with this, you can go on a date with him.
是吗?
Eh?
(红色数据动物展)红色数据动物展?
(Red Data Animal Exhibition) Red data animal exhibition?
(红色数据动物展)
(Red Data Animal Exhibition)
哇,太可爱了!
Wow, so cute!
那里一定有很多动物!嗨,这是…
There must be a lot of animals! Hey, is this...
啊?
Ah?
我不知道发生了什么事，但在这种情况下，我必须孤注一掷地选择青山。
I don't know what's going on but in this case, I must go for broke with Aoyama.
这很伤我的心。
It hurts.
啊!
Ah!
这很伤我的心……
It hurts...
A-Aoyama。
A-Aoyama.
不!我说我必须和他孤注一掷，而不是孤注一掷。
No! I said I must go for broke with him, but not physically broke.
我很抱歉。你没事吧?
I'm sorry. Are you all right?
不，应该是我道歉。青山。
No, I should be apologizing. Aoyama.
你怎么知道我的名字?
How did you know my name?
是吗?啊…
Eh? Ah...
上次我碰巧看了你的剑道比赛……
I happened to watch your kendo match last time...
哦,哦,脸!
Oh, oh, face!
哈,哈,哈。
Ha, ha, ha.
这个…
This...
你也对红色数据动物展感兴趣吧!
You're also interested in the red data animal exhibition!
我一直想去参观这个展览。
I've been longing to visit this exhibition.
嗯…青山对此很感兴趣!
Um...Aoyama is interested in this!
好吧，好吧，我有两张票。如果它是好的…
Ah, well, well, I have two tickets. If it's ok...
我可以吗?那我就高兴了!
Can I? Then I'll be glad!
谢谢你！
Thank you.
太棒了!
Great!
我很期待。
I look forward to it.
我也一样。
So do I.
我在等你，一护桃宫。
I'm waiting for you, Momomiya Ichigo.
这件衣服应该能行，对吧……
This clothes shall do the trick, right...
微笑!微笑!
Smile! Smile!
啊!
Ah!
青山!
Aoyama!
对不起,等了很长时间吗?
Sorry, waited long?
不，我也是刚来的。
No, I just came too.
然后,我们走吧。
Then, let's go.
好吧!
Okay!
青山真帅!
Aoyama is so handsome!
(红色数据动物展)
(Red Data Animal Exhibition)
(这个蓝色星球上的重要朋友)
(The important friends on this blue planet)
哇,很有趣!
Wow, interesting!
是的!
Yes!
哈哈，找到了。
Haha, there it is.
妈妈。
Mama.
太可爱了。
So cute.
嘿!
Hey!
锅!
Pan!
桃宫，谢谢你今天邀请我。
Momomiya, thank you for inviting me today.
哦,是的…
Oh, yeah...
所以你对红色数据动物很感兴趣?
So you're intrigued in red data animals?
嗯…嗯…
Hmm...well...
你是怎么被它吸引的?
How did you get intrigued by it?
嗯?
Huh?
我很抱歉。事实上，我不知道。
I-I'm sorry. Actually, I have no idea about it.
——嗯?我是偶然得到这张票的。
- Huh? - I got this ticket by chance.
所以我觉得应该会很有趣……
So I thought it should be interesting...
哈哈,我明白了。
Haha, I see.
我还是很高兴你对这个展览感兴趣。
I'm still very happy that you're interested in this exhibition.
红色数据动物是什么样的动物?
What kind of animal is the red data animal?
哦。
Oh.
这是一种可能很快就要灭绝的动物。
It's a kind of animal that may become extinct soon.
是吗?灭绝了吗?
Eh? Extinct?
是的。
Yes.
由于森林砍伐和其他开发，
Because of deforestation and other exploitations,
它们的栖息地减少了。
their habitat has decreased.
由于环境的破坏，
Due to environmental destruction,
比如非法捕鱼、海洋污染和二氧化碳的大量排放，
such as illegal fishing, ocean pollution and massive emissions of carbon dioxide,
现在我们的星球上至少有15000种野生动物
now there are at least 15,000 species of wildlife on our planet
有灭绝的危险。
that are in danger of extinction.
这些动物要消失了……
These animals are going to disappear...
是的，人类的罪行…
Yeah, the crime of human beings...
我们人类是有罪的生物。
We humans are sinful beings.
人类的罪行……
The crime of human beings...
是的……
Yep...
但是，人类和动物应该共享地球。
But, human beings and animals should be sharing the earth.
呃……
Eh...
我们一定能做些什么。
There must be something we can do.
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
嗯…我不知道。
Well...I don't know.
但我不能不管它。
But I can't leave it alone.
我不能不管它!
I can't leave it alone!
是的,完全正确!
Yes, exactly!
我们应该能做些什么。
There should be something we can do.
青山……顺便说一下，那个时候……
Aoyama...By the way, at that time...
我也觉得你有点孤独……
I also felt you're a little lonely...
最后。
Finally.
是的。
Yes.
嗯! ?
Huh!?
嗯?
Huh?
怎么了?
What's wrong?
——青山吗?——哇!
- Aoyama? - Wow!
我很抱歉!
I'm sorry!
啊,不…
Ah, no...
嗯…
Well...
I-I-I摔倒了。
I-I-I fell down.
嗯?
Huh?
现在,这种方式!
Now, this way!
啊,什么?
Ah, what?
青山!
Aoyama!
Momomiya !Momomiya !
Momomiya! Momomiya!
现在,这种方式!
Now, this way!
等待。我们要去哪里?
Wait. Where are we going?
你去前进!
Forward you go!
这是……?
Here is...?
新项目,开始!
New project, start!
什么?
What?
C-Cat吗?
C-Cat?
(东京Mew Mew New)
(Tokyo Mew Mew New)
Momomiya。
Momomiya.
Momomiya,
Momomiya。
Momomiya.
青山吗?
Aoyama?
感谢上帝。
Thanks god.
我…
I...
我来找你，你就躺在这里。
I came looking for you and you was lying down here.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
啊,我很好。
Ah, I'm fine.
紧急警铃似乎被误启动了。
The emergency bell seems to have been activated by mistake.
让我们回去。你看起来气色不好。我送你回家吧。
Let's go back. You don't look well. Let me take you home.
桃宫，我们得走了。
Momomiya, we gotta run.
好吧。
Okay.
现在!
Now!
Momomiya,下去!
Momomiya, go down!
哎哟……
Ouch...
青山!
Aoyama!
你的怪物。走开!
You monster. Go away!
啊…等待…
Ah...Wait...
哦不，哦不，哦不!朝我来了，朝我来了。
Oh no, oh no, oh no! It's coming at me, it's coming at me.
你比你看起来要重。
You are heavier than you look.
奇美拉·阿尼玛就是在这个时候出现的。
Chimera Anima came out at such a time.
真不是时候。不，时机很好。
What a bad timing. No, it's a good timing.
Momomiya草莓。
Momomiya Ichigo.
你怎么知道我的名字?
W-why do you know my name?
你到底是谁?
Who on earth are you?
我的名字是Shirogane Ryou。
My name is Shirogane Ryou.
没有时间了。以后我会解释。现在打败那东西!
There is no time. Later I'll explain. Now defeat that thing!
——Rua !——啊!
- Rua! - Ah!
青山!
Aoyama!
——啊!——傻瓜!
- Ah! - Idiot!
是的。她唤醒了!
Yes. She's awakened!
这是什么?
What is this?
喵喵一护，变形!
Mew Mew Ichigo, Metamorphosis!
哎哟……
Ouch...
啊? !
Ah?!
这是什么? !
What is this?!
带薄荷呼应!
Ribbon Mint Echo!
新草莓,战斗!
Mew Ichigo, fight!
是你给我的票吗?
You are the one who gave me the tickets?
战斗?我吗?
Fight? Me?
是的。如果我们不打败这个Chinera阿尼玛，
Yes. If we don't defeat this Chinera Anima,
他会有危险的!
he will be in danger!
拥有你初吻的人受伤了可以吗?
Is it okay if the person owning your first kiss gets hurt?
Fir-first吻吗?
Fir-first kiss?
我摔倒的时候不小心亲了一下。
It was just an accidental k-kiss when I fell down.
我一直幻想着初吻，但这太突然了。
Well, I've been always fancying about first kiss, but it's all of a sudden.
现在不是说这种话的时候!
Now is not the time to say that kind of thing!
诸如此类的事情!?
That kind of thing!?
对于一个女孩来说，初吻是一生只有一次的重要事情!
For a girl, the first kiss is a once-in-a-lifetime important thing!
没错，但是现在……
That is right, but now...
啊~我应该去一个更浪漫的地方约会!
Ah~I should have gone to a more romantic place for a date!
手牵手，凝视彼此的眼睛!在那之后还有许多其他的事情!但是…
Hand in hand, gazing into each others' eyes! And many other things after that! But...
-你怎么补偿?-不是我毁了它!
- How can you compensate that? - Not me who ruined it!
这两个可以吗?
Will it be OK for these two?
好了!
Nice!
我是怎么做到的?
Um, how did I do that?
现在!我相信这句话已经进入了你的脑海。
Now! I'm sure the words have come to your mind.
单词吗?
Words?
即使你说…
Even if you say that...
嗯…草莓浆果?
Hmm... Strawberry berry?
这是什么?
What is this?
足够了。我正在生气。
Enough. I'm getting annoyed.
嘿,嘿。那边的怪物!
Hey, hey. The monster over there!
你竟敢伤害我的青山!
How dare you hurt my Aoyama!
在充满感激,
In full gratitude,
我将为您服务。
I'll be of service.
带草莓检查!
Ribbon Strawberry Check!
好!
Good!
她做到了!
She did it!
楚!
Chu!
外星人恢复!
Alien recovered!
谢谢你,R2000。
Thank you, R2000.
欢迎你!
You're welcome!
哟!
Yo!
你努力工作。
You've worked hard.
这是一个巨大的成功!
It's a great success!
是的!但它是可怕的。
Yes! But it's scary.
这不是我的错。
It's not my fault.
发生什么事了!
What is going on!
给我解释一下!
Explain it to me!
我为什么要穿成这样去打怪物?
Why do I have to dress up like this to fight monsters?
听!
Listen!
嗯?
Huh?
你已经被选中了。
You have been chosen.
做正义的捍卫者，保护地球!
To be a champion of justice and protect the earth!
保护地球?
Protect the earth?
我……
Me...
是的。
Yes.
但是，即使你突然这么说……
But, even if you said that suddenly...
我会告诉你一切的。跟我来。
I will tell you everything. Follow me.
等等!你要带我去哪?
Wait! Where are you taking me?
你不能这样做，瑞尤。
You can't do it like that, Ryou.
嗯?
Huh?
你得好好做这位女士的护花使者。
You need to be the lady's escort properly.
Keiichiro……
Keiichiro...
很高兴第一次见到你。殿下。
Nice to meet you for the first time. Your Highness.
我叫赤坂庆一郎。
My name is Akasaka Keiichiro.
桃宫一护小姐，我真诚地请求您的理解。
Miss Momomiya Ichigo, I ask for your understanding sincerely.
请把你的命运托付给我们。
Please entrust your fate to us.
啊? !
Huh?!
好吧,让我们离开。
Well, let's depart.
我不能!我必须帮助青山。
I can't! And I have to help Aoyama.
你要怎么跟他解释你为什么穿成那样?
How are you gonna explain to him why you're dressing like that?
是吗?啊…
Eh? Ah...
别担心。他只是被敲晕了。
Don't worry. He was just knocked unconscious.
把他交给我们吧。
Leave him to us.
把他交给我吧。
Leave him to me.
他现在是你的了，Mew Minto。
He's yours now, Mew Minto.
现在。一护小姐，请跟我们来。
Now. Miss Ichigo, please come with us.
啊……好吧……
Ah...okay...
青山……
Aoyama...
他们要带我去哪?
Where are they gonna take me?
我不应该跟着他们……
I shouldn't have followed them...
但是，我不能以这种状态回家。
But, I can't go home in this state.
我该怎么办?
What should I do?
这些人可能在计划……
These people might be planning...
把我当实验对象!
to use me as a test subject!
我还没有正式的约会。不!
I haven't had a proper date. No!
现在就让我走!
Let me go right now!
还我青春!
Give me back my youth!
天啊。你可能真的很吵。
Geez. You can be really noisy.
好了，下车吧。
Alright, get off now.
这个地方是什么?
This place is?
欢迎来到喵喵咖啡馆。
Welcome to Mew Mew Cafe.
也是我们的安全屋。
And our safe house.
嗯? !
Eh?!
下一集:
The next episode:
“什么是真正的朋友?”
"What is a true friend?"
(什么是真正的朋友?)
(What Is a True Friend?)